Code:
	0.	In order to run our top performing classifier LR-5, please run the jupyter notebook called "RUNME_LR_5" in the LR-5 code folder. This will return classifications for each (video, rater) pair. We did further analysis on it by picking an overall classification of each video using majority rules and calculating results accordingly.
	0.	In order to run the video feature classifier, LR-VF, please run the jupyter notebook called "LR_VF" which walks through the methods used to construct the classifier.

Each of the directories uses example data to run the code.