LR-5, our top performing classifier, is trained on clinical data generated through the administration of ADOS M2 and was tested in a previous study:
https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC5735531/

In this study, we validate LR-5 on video features, instead of clinical features, to reduce it to practice. Instructions on how to run the code:

Please run the jupyter notebook called "RUNME_LR_5" in the LR-5 folder. This will return classifications for each (video, rater) pair. We did further analysis on it by picking an overall classification of each video using majority rules and caalculating results accordingly.
